I can also click on "Create" over here and as you see I can upload image or I can create
images, edit images, icons, you know, all of them are available over here as well.
So Microsoft Designer is a pretty powerful tool, you know, if I want to be honest with you.
And it provides us with plenty of possibilities.
So in this very lecture I try my best to go through the top and the most used ones, you
know.
And about the rest I want you guys to try to like practice yourselves, you know, and
try to figure out the platform yourselves.
So we are going to go through the main and the base, you know, and the foundational parts
of Microsoft Designer.
But when it comes to the extra parts I want you guys to try your best to go through them
as well.